<Document>
  # Threshold Cargo
  This guide will explain the many special mechanics you must navigate when importing, exporting or working a cargo job in the Threshold.

  ## Trade Stations
  In the Threshold we rely on imports to provide the crucial goods that we cannot produce ourselves and we rely on exports to provide money for our local economy.
  We can't rely on a single trade station to source all of our imports and exports but luckily there are many trade stations scattered around the Threshold.

  ### Imports
  Goods can be imported from any cargo request computer.
  You dont need to be a Quartermaster to approve orders as anyone can spend their own hard earned money to approve orders at a cargo request computer.

  The cargo request computer has an option to choose which trade station you are importing from.
  Trade stations have very different inventories from one another and those inventories can be improved if the trade station levels up.
  When a cargo order is approved it appears on the trade station that it was ordered from.

  Some trade stations are very far away and may require a well equipped vessel to safely reach.
  The closest trade station to where you first arrive is the Nanotrasen trade station.
  Before you place an import order make sure the trade station you are buying from is reachable or else your goods may be stranded or stolen.

  ### Exports
  Goods can be sold at any trade station for cash or to direct deposit into a faction account.
  Exporting without fufilling a cargo bounty occurs a heafty price penalty in the Threshold.

  ### Bounties
  Any individual or faction is free to pursue cargo bounties in the Threshold, provided they can get the goods to the trade station that offers the bounty.
  There are a wide variety of bounties in the Threshold and different types of trade stations offer different types of bounties.
  Bounties in the Threshold are spawned on a two and a half hour cycle. Make sure you will have enough time to complete a bounty before starting it.

  A bounty [bold]must be brought to the trade station that offered it[/bold] to be completed.
  The closest trade station to where you first arrive is the Nanotrasen trade station.

  ### Trade Station Control
  When a faction controls a trade station the trade station provides more bounties and starts to earn XP towards leveling up.
  When bounties are completed a trade station gains XP and when bounties expire without being completed the trade station loses XP.
  Factions may set an import and export tax on their trade station which is deposited directly into their account.
  Factions earn a lot of passive income when they control a high level trade station.

</Document>

